Motion to approve.
Michael.
John.
I.
Parker.
Ten.
The session possible.
I.
Regarding proposed Oklahoma National Gas.
Along the street to the east of the airport.
I have been in contact with Dustin Frederick of O.N.G.
And he has gotten the approval of the power that the two offer a $20,000.
The.
An exchange for a grant of the easement.
And they will come in and help us.
A tip to institute a franchise where in our percentage would be increased from.
Two percent to either three or four percent.
We have it.
Obviously that would all be negotiated at the time that the franchise is passed.
Is it for that new pipeline that's going on by their report?
Yes, sir.
Sir, sir again.
Are you, sir?
So O.N.G.
Will pay the city $20,000 for the easement.
And then after that is done.
They will assist us with.
The franchise.
We would have to.
I can't say they will help us get a franchise because that has to get to the.
But they will come in and work with us.
Help us do it and pay for the vote that we have to have.
And they are.
Mr. Frederick has acknowledged that 2 percent is below the state average.
So we would increase our percentage of collections from O.N.G.
Gatsails.
But at least 1 percent and.
Probably 2 percent.
Which would amount to about.
100.
And extra $100,000 revenue here.
Just from looking at what other cities charge the.
And a couple of their cities.
I've been had were like after so many years.
The city could buy out the utility.
If they wanted.
To take it over.
Do you know what?
Prior has their own gas.
We don't have to move the fence or anything.
We're at it.
Just a little side of the fence.
Correct.
And so that's from.
Where to where.
Just along that fence.
5,000 something.
Yeah.
But it comes over from behind sector.
And into the front.
Done that one row.
do a cross or how's it come, how's it how they you know currently runs down the river
tracks of what they said and so they're gonna cross and over etc. I don't know
what that's crossing. It would actually be Hopkins. Hopkins? Yeah. Okay, the
side to graveyard cemetery? No, they're going by Hopkins and then they're gonna
turn and go down. You know I'm saying no, I'm going to be going down the road
the concrete plan is on. Oh, by the concrete plan? That part. Yeah, but they're
gonna you know they're they're bought they've purchased the easement from Hopkins
right there so they know they're gonna have like their station or whatever they
said and then they would turn and I'm going down the road. On down by Westcoe, correct?
That's where it is currently.
Yeah, it's gonna be at Hopkins. It's gonna be at Hopkins and Hopkins has settled according to
you know, and if the board has a different number I mean we're happy to go back to them.
What's a lot better and what they gave us before? What'd you say?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that was my biggest concern, you know, being good neighbors is we don't want
to agree to anything. Yeah, we're talking about the summer period.
We too. The other side is the franchise. So we're doing it on my two things. So the
franchise agreement is when we've just like pulled some cities, Travis up, pull some cities and
they were getting in my from what 3.25, the 4.25 person, you know. Yeah, so then you know, the only way to go
higher is by friends or the 20,000 is just for the easement so that's a separate. So they're
I'm here.
No land management here.
The land management actually, the two representatives who are here were not authorized to be here that night.
Really?
I don't know.
Imagine that.
I make a motion to approve.
11.
This may have been being changed from counter chambers and reclaim the six-center gym for a tour and discussion
that is really a bit of a gym.
It is beautiful if you haven't seen it.
First, me and me have that rapply metallic out there more now.
I don't know.
14.
If any, which is a residence is opposing this agenda, 15 staff reports, 16 mayor, council community,
announcements.
Okay.
So, we're going to be somewhat different tonight for me.
A lot of times, our firefighters, our police officers, our same police, and nothing
but negative.
And I know that's got to be disheartening at some times because a lot of good things have
them from our police.
And one was brought to my attention.
And we're going to celebrate tonight.
And deserve to be celebrated.
And it's a really cool thing.
I got a text message.
They brought me a private message from a gentleman.
And he told me that he died in our firefighters' life.
And he had been transferred to Mercy Hospital.
And he's the name of the Mercy Mirror.
The Mercy City should not survive in our firefighters and I know they don't do what they do to be celebrated
They do what they do because they love it and I want to help our community
But so often
These guys see bad stuff
They see somebody's house burning the ground
They see somebody that was a car wreck that didn't make it in this case
When they dropped this gentleman off the hospital they didn't know if he was going to make it
We did and I went to church last Wednesday
Not knowing that gentleman at all as in the message we've exchanged and I told him that message that God wouldn't done with him
And that's why still here
God had a purpose for him
So he's here tonight
He was in my son. He was in my men's class that was denied when I walked in so I got to meeting face to face and he got to tell his story again to that men's group
And the leader of that men's group here Mr. Steve Engelbrecht and Tom Jarvis is the man
And he asked me if he could come here tonight and talk and he wanted the firefighters here to say his life
And they're also in the room
So Tom if you'd like to go out to the podium and and you're welcome to tell your story
And underbistle and fire Parker for the two firefighters guys
Would you guys let's go up and stand by Tom
Thank you for those guys.
Thank you for starting our community.
We appreciate you guys.
And again, I know you don't do this for this, but Tom wanted the opportunity to thank
you and I felt like it was something we needed to do.
So thank you guys for sort of mind.
We appreciate you.
17.
City of Mayors for Communications.
Nonsense.
All right.
18.
This means I'll be continued from the Kelp Tigers to the right.
We're in the staff room for the purpose of the executive session.